it's been about a week since I did my
hundred apples actually 98 apples I have
two more to do to add to make it a
official 100 and so I've written a lot
of things down on random pieces of paper
throughout the week I wanted them to be
special ones but I guess it's like
hoarding apples it's not like our Deen
apples that's the definition of hoarding
apples is holding the back toe something
special I guess it's the opposite having
something special and not give me a note
to the world but the other one that's
what I was doing this is a random video
Marni rambling considerably I went to
Aboriginal days at Trout Lake today and
one of my ideas which is I've already
touched on which is the historical
website but more focused I want to know
how to look into my own roots find out
who my Celtic side was before
Christianity Catholicism took over and
burned all the witches and stopped all
the people looking off the land I also
want to know about my Jewish ancestry
and how to I mean I know Jewish friends
I can go to synagogue I could go and do
all of that it interests me less because
it's a religion that the cultural stuff
and trust me though being able to find
out more about that would be interesting
as well as my First Nations which is
Cherokee which is not was here in
Vancouver the ones in Vancouver are the
coastal ones and got to go on a canoe
today I'm going to do but the idea for
the app the website is a I don't even
know just just something that helps me
and more understands really my tribe
here sorry that piece of
my injury understanding how the
different tribes differ what their
artwork is like what their food was like
but their territory was where their
history and where they kind of you know
expanded to and retracted to I would
like a First Nations interactive history
that tells the stories of all of our
ancestors back through all the time so
yeah
Apple number I don't wonder that was 98
an hour yeah whatever
Apple bonus one which fills in one place